Inventory of the Mills E. Godwin Jr. Papers 1947-1989
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Speeches, 1957-1978. (Box 17-24)
  - Speeches, 1974., 138 items. (Box 20)
    - Opening Session, VFW Convention, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 21 June 1974. (Box 20)
    - Lynchburg Foundry-Archer Creek, Campbell County, 26 June 1974. (Box 20)
    - EXPO '74, Open Air Theatre, 28 June 1974. (Box 20)
    - Chamber of Commerce, EXPO '74, 28 June 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Day, EXPO '74, Formal Dinner, 28 June 1974. (Box 20)
    - Volvo Groundbreaking Ceremony, Chesapeake, Virginia, 2 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - Swearing-in Ceremony, U. S. Navy, Virginia Company, State Capitol, 10 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of Bicentennial Center and Museum, Alexandria, Virginia, 11 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - Welcoming Remarks, American Peanut Research and Education Association, Hilton 1776 Inn, Williamsburg, Virginia, 15 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - The Virginia Bar Association Meeting, Introduction of Vice-President Ford, The Homestead, 20 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - Statement in support of Interstate 66, Office of Senator William L. Scott, Washington, D. C., 29 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - Introduction of Sir Peter Ramsbotham, British Ambassador to the United States, First Assembly Day at Jamestown, 31 July 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, The Homestead, 2 August 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Clerks Association, Hilton Inn 1776, Williamsburg, Virginia, 9 August 1974. (Box 20)
    - Local Government officials Conference, University of Virginia, Institute of Government, Newcomb Hall, Charlottesville, Virginia, 26 August 1974. (Box 20)
    - AAA Pedestrian Safety Awards Luncheon, Richmond Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 3 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Remarks at the Reconvening of the First Continental Congress, Carpenters' Hall, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 5-6 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Remarks as President of First Continental Congress, Re-enactment, Carpenters' Hall, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 5 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Remarks as Chairman of the First Continental Congress 1974 Carpenters' Hall, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 6 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Adjournment of First Continental Congress Re-enactment, Carpenters' Hall, Philadelphia, 6 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Recognition Dinner for Chief Justice Snead, Hotel John Marshall, 6 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Rural Area Development Session, Southern Governors' Conference, 9 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia's Corrections Program, Lakeway-World of Tennis, Texas Meeting, Southern Governors' Conference, 10 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - UGF Kickoff for State of Virginia Employees, 16 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Southeastern Regional Conference, American Public Welfare Association, New Cavalier, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 18 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Richmond Bar Association, Hotel John Marshall, Marshall Room, 19 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Jefferson Awards Banquet, John Marshall Hotel Richmond, Virginia, 20 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Municipal League, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 22 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of New Buildings, Petersburg Training School and Hospital, 25 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 27 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Halftime - VPI, Blacksburg, Virginia, 28 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - Governor's Day, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Virginia, 28 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - United Givers Fund Kick-Off, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 30 September 1974. (Box 20)
    - "Operation Independence" Hearings, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of William F. Stone Building, Patrick Henry Community College, Martinsville, Virginia, 2 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Petroleum Jobbers Association, Cavalier Oceanfront, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 7 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Inauguration of Frank L. Hereford, Jr., University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, 9 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - 26th Annual Virginia Conference on World Trade, Sheraton Inn, Reston, Virginia, 10 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Completion of Sanger Hall and Tompkins McCaw Library, Medical College of Virginia of VCU, Richmond, Virginia, 11 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Second Annual Historic, Appomattox Railroad Festival, Appomattox, Virginia, 12 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Second Annual Historic Appomattox Railroad Festival, Falling River Country Club, Appomattox, Virginia, 12 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of Phase II Buildings, Blue Ridge Community College, Weyers Cave, Virginia (Mr. Maurice B. Rowe, Governor's Secretary of Administration and Finance, gave this speech), 16 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dairymen, Inc., Southeast Division, Barter Theatre (speech given by Mr. Mason Carbaugh, Director of the Department of Agriculture and Commerce), 17 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Order of the White Jacket, William and Mary College, Williamsburg, Virginia, 17 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Site Dedication, DMV Headquarters Building, Richmond, 18 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of Gray Court, University of Richmond, Richmond, Virginia, 18 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of Eastern Shore Community College, Melfa, Virginia, 19 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Governors' Awards Banquet, Hotel Chamberlin (speech given by Lieutenant Governor John N. Dalton on behalf of the governor), 19 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Introduction of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Virginia State Chamber of Commerce and Virginia Farm Bureau Stop Inflation Now Conference, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 23 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Script of Personnel Filming, 23 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Symposium, Public-Private Higher Education in Virginia, Martha Washington Inn, Abingdon, Virginia, 24 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Highway Conference, 24 October 1974. (Box 20)
    - Kenneth Robinson Rally, 1 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, Richmond, Virginia, 2 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Tidewater Virginia Billy Graham Crusade, Hampton Roads Coliseum, 3 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Travel Reception, Hemisphere Club, Time-Life Building, Rockefeller Center, New York, New York, 6 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Twenty-Third Annual Report to Top Management Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria, New York, New York, 7 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Governor's Conference on Energy, Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 8 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Thomas Nelson Community College, Hampton, Virginia, 10 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - "Financing Industrial Growth in Virginia", Annual Meeting Southern Growth Policies Board, Atlanta, Georgia, 13 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of Reynolds Recycling Plant, Williamsburg, Virginia, 15 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Scottish Rite Banquet, Staunton, Virginia, 16 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Report to Agriculture and Business Dinner, Suffolk Chamber of Commerce, Suffolk, National Guard Armory, 18 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Retreat for State Agency Heads, Airlie, Warrenton, Virginia, 18 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Accreditation Seminar, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 20 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of F & M Center, Richmond, Virginia (plus suggested beginning of F & M speech for governor's disposal), 20 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Consumers Conference, Hyatt House, Richmond, 21 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Annual Meeting, The Virginia League for Planned Parenthood, The Richmond Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 22 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Joint Meeting of Newport News Kiwanis Club and Newport News Rotary Club, Jefferson Avenue Holiday Inn, Newport News, Virginia, 26 November 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication Fauquier County Court and Office Building, Warrenton, Virginia, 8 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Introduction of FBI Director, Clarence M. Kelley, 9 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Driver Improvement Program Lunch, Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 9 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Governor Dunn Appreciation Dinner, Memphis Auditorium, Memphis, Tennessee, 10 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Annual Convention, Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 10 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Colon Club Breakfast, 13 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication of Memorial Highway Marker of Robert F. Baldwin Toll Booth, Virginia Beach-Norfolk Expressway, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 14 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Launching of "Virginia", Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company, 14 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, State Capitol, 18 December 1974. (Box 20)
    - Dedication East River Mountain Tunnel, Bluefield, West Virginia, 20 December 1974. (Box 20)
  - Speeches, 1975., 114 items. (Box 21)
    - Deans and Dental Examiners, Williamsburg, Virginia, 4 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Richmond Kiwanis Club, Richmond, Virginia, 6 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Address to the General Assembly, 8 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Roanoke Valley Chamber of Commerce, Roanoke, Virginia, 9 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, John Marshall Hotel, 14 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - The Industry Relations Committee Conference on Virginia Industry Job Training and Employment of the Deaf, Richmond, Virginia, 15 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Introduction of Herman E. Talmadge, Georgia U. S. Senator, Agri-Business Appreciation Banquet, John Marshall Hotel, 15 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Association of Colleges, Hotel Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 17 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Bayside Hospital Dedication, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 19 January 1975. (Box 21)
    - Conference on Stimulating Local Economy through Public Service Employment, Hotel John Marshall, 5 February 1975. (Box 21)
    - National Bicentennial Debates Award Banquet, Williamsburg Conference Center, 7 February 1975. (Box 21)
    - Closing Speech to General Assembly, 22 February 1975. (Box 21)
    - Staunton-Augusta County Chamber of Commerce, Ingleside Red Carpet Inn, Staunton, Virginia, 18 March 1975. (Box 21)
    - "Cost of Electricity" - Governor's TV Address, 19 March 1975. (Box 21)
    - Savings Bond Drive Kick-Off, Highway Auditorium, Richmond, Virginia, 27 March 1975. (Box 21)
    - Shenandoah Valley Travel Association, Winchester, Virginia, 27 March 1975. (Box 21)
    - Challenge for Highway Safety, 1 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Retirement Dinner, Colonel E. P. Gill, Chief of Police, Chesterfield County, Cloverhill High School, 1 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Joint Session of Model General Assembly, State Capitol, 3 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication of Virginia Beach Campus, Tidewater Community College, 6 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Annual Joint Dinner Meeting, Peninsula Rotary Clubs, Chamberlin Hotel, 10 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Inauguration of Prince B. Woodard, President of Mary Washington College, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 11 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Electoral Board Association, Sheraton Motor Inn, Richmond, Virginia, 19 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Conference on Volunteerism, Holiday Inn West, Richmond, Virginia, 19 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication Southeastern Virginia Training Center for the Mentally Retarded, Chesapeake, Virginia, 23 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Credit Union Convention, John Marshall Hotel, 25 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication Science Building, Madison College, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 26 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Introduction of Senatory Henry Bellmon, Commonwealth Day Dinner, Marriott Twin Bridges Motel, 26 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - State Conference on Gerontology, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 28 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Farmville Chamber of Commerce, Wedgewood Country Club, 28 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Harvard Club of Virginia, Windsor House, Richmond, Virginia, 30 April 1975. (Box 21)
    - Buckingham County Day, Buckingham County High School, 3 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - State Agency Luncheon, 5 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Senior Citizens Day, Richmond Coliseum, 6 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Cornerstone Laying, Yorktown Bicentennial Center, 10 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Commencement, old Dominion University, Norfolk, Virginia, 11 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Babcock and Wilcox Addition, 13 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - President's Reception, Martinsville-Henry Chamber of Commerce, Martinsville, Virginia, 13 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Fund Raising Luncheon MCV Cancer Center, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 14 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Judicial Conference of Virginia, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 22 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Commencement, Virginia Wesleyan College, Norfolk, Virginia, 24 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Joint Dinner Meeting, State Board of Health and Comprehensive Health Planning Council, 27 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Mocha Temple #7 Regional Gala Day Celebration, 29 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Saint Luke's Church, 31 May 1975. (Box 21)
    - Commencement, Randolph Macon College, Ashland, Virginia, 1 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Operation Sail, Aircraft Carrier John F. Kennedy, 13 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Bankers Association, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 14 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication Botetourt Courthouse, 14 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Culpeper Bicentennial Commission, Culpeper, Virginia, 20 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - I-66 Hearing, Washington, D. C., 21 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Appreciation Dinner for Dr. Mack I. Shanholtz, Commonwealth Club, Richmond, Virginia, 23 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Fraternal Order of Eagles, 68th Annual Convention, 3rd and Marshall Streets, Richmond, Virginia, 27 June 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication of New Headquarters, Koger Executive Center, Three Chopt Road and Forest Avenue, Henrico County, Virginia, 11 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Home Builders Association of Virginia, Cavalier Oceanfront, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 12 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Comments to House Appropriations Committee, 14 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Opening Ceremonies, Ribbon Cutting I-195, 15 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Farewell Dinner, Governor's School for the Gifted, Mary Washington College, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 18 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Truck Association Executive Council, Williamsburg Lodge, Williamsburg, Virginia, 21 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Meeting of Byrd Memorial Finance Committee, 22 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - PBX International Convention, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 24 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - First Assembly Day, Jamestown, 29 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Southern Legislative Conference, Council of State Governments, State Dinner, Conference Center, Colonial Williamsburg, 31 July 1975. (Box 21)
    - Conference of Chief Justices and State Court Administrators, The Homestead, 4 August 1975. (Box 21)
    - Second Annual Virginia Aviation Conference, The Homestead, 22 August 1975. (Box 21)
    - Annual Safety Awards Luncheon, Richmond Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 9 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Annual Fall Conference, Education Association, Rehabilitative School Authority, 11 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - 25th Anniversary Dinner, Ashland Volunteer Rescue Squad, Ashland War Memorial Building, 12 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Southern Governors Conference, 17 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Thomas Jefferson Awards Banquet, Old Dominion Chapter Public Relations Society of America, U. S. Navy Station Commissioned Officers Mess, Norfolk, Virginia, 18 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Remarks to the News Media on the Budget, 19 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Bill Tuck Day, Halifax Fairgrounds, Stew Luncheon, 20 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Municipal League, Norfolk, Virginia, 22 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication of Clarence Johnston Robinson Hall, George Mason University, Fairfax, Virginia, 24 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - United Way Kick-Off, Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Highways Auditorium, 24 September 1975. (Box 21)
    - Peter Muhlenberg Day, Woodstock, Virginia, 1 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Conference on Law-related Education, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 3 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Scottish Rite Council Dinner, Stouffer's National Center Inn, Arlington, Virginia, 4 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Regional Directors for Spruce Up Virginia, Philip Morris Plant, Richmond, Virginia, 7 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - First Virginia Conference on Local Environmental Management, Hotel John Marshall, 9 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Order of The White Jacket, Williamsburg, Virginia, 9 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication of The Tidewater Occupational Center, Suffolk, Virginia, 14 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Suffolk Bicentennial, Peanut Park, 14 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Section, American Water Works Association, Hyatt House, Richmond, Virginia, 15 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Fredericksburg Bicentennial Celebration, George Washington Hall, Mary Washington College, 15 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Inauguration of Dr. William E. Lavery, President Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Virginia, 16 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Fifth Annual Festival of Leaves, Front Royal, Virginia, 18 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 20 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Retired Teachers Association, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 22 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, Doubleday and Company, Inc., Orange, Virginia, 22 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Remarks made on the occasion of the visit of Lord Lothian, Chairman of the British Bicentennial Liaison Committee to Yorktown and Williamsburg, 23 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Economic Development Institute Briefing, State Capitol, 24 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Annual Awards Banquet, Virginia Wildlife Federation, Mariner Resort Motel Inn, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 25 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication of P. D. Pruden Vocational Technical Center, Suffolk, Virginia, 26 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Alkaline Pulping Conference of the Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Williamsburg Conference Center, Williamsburg, Virginia, 27 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Remarks to Community College President, J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 30 October 1975. (Box 21)
    - Inauguration of Kiwanis International Bicentennial Program, Williamsburg Lodge, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Day, Capitol Steps, Washington, D. C., 2 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - 27th Annual Virginia Woman's Forum, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 7 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Founder's Day Convocation, Virginia Military Institute, 11 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Senator Harry F. Byrd Anniversary Dinner, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 11 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - New York Travel Writers, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, 12 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Salute to Top Management, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, New York City, 13 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Annual Meeting Virginia Road Builders' Association, Williamsburg, Virginia, 14 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Inauguration of Harrison B. Wilson, Jr., as President of Norfolk State College, Chrysler Hall, Norfolk, Virginia, 23 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Installation of Rev. William M. Everhart, Oakland Christian Church, Chuckatuck, Virginia, 23 November 1975. (Box 21)
    - Inauguration of Dr. T. Edward Temple, President of Virginia Commonwealth University, Richmond, Virginia, 4 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Commemoration, Battle of Great Bridge, Chesapeake Civic Center, Chesapeake, Virginia, 6 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Groundbreaking, Basic Medical Education Building, Eastern Virginia Medical Authority, Norfolk, Virginia, 9 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts Banquet, Sheraton Motor Inn, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 9 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Brotherhood Citation Dinner, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 10 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Dedication Ceremony Life Insurance Company of Virginia Building at Brookfield, Richmond, Virginia, 11 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting, State Capitol, 16 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Graduation Exercises, Department of Public Safety, Division of Police, Third Basic Training Academy, Henrico Police Department, 19 December 1975. (Box 21)
    - Presentation of the Jimmy Doolittle Fellow Award, Aerospace Education Foundation, Nielson's Restaurant, Richmond, Virginia, 22 December 1975. (Box 21)
  - Speeches, 1976., 140 items. (Box 22-23)
    - Bicentennial, New Hampshire Constitution, Concord, New Hampshire, 5 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Opening of the Ski Slope, Wintergreen Recreational Community, Nelson County, Virginia, 6 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Phyllis Galanti Day, Non-Commissioned Officers' Club, Blackstone, Virginia, 9 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Testimonial Dinner for Steve and Chrysa Sacalis, Sacalis Hall, Newport News, Virginia, 11 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Message to the 1976 General Assembly, State Capitol, 14 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Budget Briefing, House Chambers, State Capitol, 17 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - North Wing Dedication, Virginia Museum, 19 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Council of Churches, Prayer Breakfast, St. Paul's Episcopal Church, Richmond, Virginia, 21 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Testimony before the United States Senate Subcommittee on Agricultural Research and General Legislation of the Senate Committee on Agriculture and Forestry, 22 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Bicentennial Agribusiness Appreciation Banquet, State Fair Grounds, 24 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Associated General Contractors, The Homestead, Hot Springs, Virginia, 26 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Association of Electric Corporatives, Unsung Virginian Award Luncheon, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 27 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Association of Virginia colleges, Richmond Hyatt House Annual Meeting and Awards Luncheon, Keep Virginia Beautiful, Inc., John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 28 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Commemorative Session of the General Assembly, House of Burgesses, Williamsburg, Virginia, 31 January 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 5 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - National Bicentennial Debates Dinner, Williamsburg, Virginia, 6 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Charter Day Bicentennial Observance, College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia, 7 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association Dinner, Valle's Restaurant, Richmond, Virginia, 10 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, Holiday Inn, Richmond, Virginia, 16 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Tastee-Freeze Big T Convention, Hotel John Marshall, Richmond, Virginia, 17 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Society for Professional Engineers, Mount Vernon Inn, Mount Vernon, Virginia, 28 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Opening of New Wing, Chrysler Museum, Norfolk, Virginia, 29 February 1976. (Box 22)
    - Newcomen Society in North America, Dinner, Williamsburg Lodge, Williamsburg, Virginia, 5 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Message from the governor to the House Courts of Justice Committee, 8 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Washington Cathedral, Washington, D. C., 8 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Tobacco, Farm Equipment and Services Exposition, Clarksville, Virginia, 10 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Address to members of the General Assembly at close of session, 13 March 1976. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Trial Lawyers' Association Banquet, Williamsburg, 20 March 1976. (Box 22)